[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[doorbell ringing]
[门铃响]
- Gosh! Who's at the door this early?
- 天哪！这么早谁在门口？
- Hi. - Aah!
- 嗨。 - 啊！
- Sharon Dee, BCD TV. Can we get a comment from JT?
- 莎伦·迪，BCD电视台。我们能从JT那里得到一些评论吗？
- Okay, you're just saying letters.
- 好吧，你只是在说字母。
- Rumor has it action mega hunk JT Steele,
- 传闻中，动作巨星JT·斯蒂尔，
star of the "Mission: Not Do-able" movies,
《不可能的任务》系列电影的明星，
is hiding here researching his next role.
据说藏在这里为他的下一个角色做研究。
- Did someone say JT Steele? - Yes, I did.
- 有人提到JT·斯蒂尔吗？ - 是的，我提到了。
Sharon Dee, BCD TV. Is he here?
莎伦·迪，BCD电视台。他在这里吗？
- Is who here? - JT Steele.
- 谁在这里？ - JT·斯蒂尔。
- JT Steele's here? - JT Steele's not here.
- JT·斯蒂尔在这里？ - JT·斯蒂尔不在这里。
- JT Steele's here? - Who's at the door?
- JT·斯蒂尔在这里？ - 谁在门口？
- Sharon Dee, BCD TV. She's asking about JT.
- 莎伦·迪，BCD电视台。她在问关于JT的事。
- Hey, who's at the door?
- 嘿，谁在门口？
- I think you got a bad tip.
- 我觉得你得到了错误的消息。
The closest thing we have to a movie star is...
我们这里最接近电影明星的是...
him.
他。
- Perhaps you've seen the commercials
- 也许你看过汤姆的“运动起来”的广告？
for Tom's Get Sporty? - Nope.
是为汤姆的Get Sporty做广告的？ - 没听说过。
- Oh, well, they go a little something like this:
- 哦，好吧，它们大概是这样的：
"Hi. I'm Tom.
“嗨。我是汤姆。
"We're having a sale this week on tube socks.
“这周我们店里袜子大减价。
Tell your friends."
告诉你的朋友们。”
- Okay, what was that all about?
- 好吧，那是什么意思？
- That was pretty weird.
- 那真是挺奇怪的。
- Hey, thanks for working in the plug for the store, "Tom."
- 嘿，谢谢你在店里为“汤姆”打广告。
- Oh, no problem...
- 哦，没问题...
Tom.
汤姆。
- Two Dads?
- 两个爸爸？
Okay, this just went from weird to...ah...!
好吧，这从奇怪变成了...啊...！
- Well, things are about to go from "ah!" to "whoa!"
- 嗯，事情即将从“啊！”变成“哇！”
- That's right...
- 没错...
because I'm...
因为我是...
JT Steele.
JT 斯蒂尔。
kids: Whoa!
孩子们：哇！
- Told ya.
- 告诉过你了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ One, two ♪ ♪ One, two, three four ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 一，二，三，四 ♪
[upbeat music]
- Kids, I would like to formally introduce you
孩子们，我想正式向你们介绍
to my old pal Fan's Choice Award-winner...
我的老朋友，Fan's Choice Award得主...
JT Steele!
JT Steele！
- This is so cool!
这太酷了！
How do you guys know each other?
你们是怎么认识的？
- Ah, Real Tom used to babysit me.
啊，Real Tom以前给我当过保姆。
- Easiest gig ever.
有史以来最轻松的工作。
One glass of warm milk, and this little fella
一杯温牛奶，这小家伙
was out like a light. - It's true.
就睡得像灯一样亮。——是真的。
The moo-juice sends me straight to Z-Town.
那杯牛奶直接把我送到了Z镇。
[gasping]
[喘气声]
- Ow! - Oh, no!
- 哎哟！ - 哦，不！
- Are you okay? - I'm good.
- 你还好吗？ - 我没事。
- Wait a minute.
- 等一下。
- How do we know this is actually JT Steele?
- 我们怎么知道这真的是JT·斯蒂尔？
And how do we know that you're Dad?
- 还有，我们怎么知道你是爸爸？
- Don't! Oh!
- 别！哦！
Dicky, that's real face!
迪基，那是真脸！
- That's what they all say. - Dicky, that is your father!
- 他们都是这么说的。 - 迪基，那真的是你爸爸！
- Yeah, but who are you? [yelling]
是的，但你是谁？
- Nicky, that's Mom.
尼基，那是妈妈。
- Let's settle this once and for all.
让我们一劳永逸地解决这个问题。
JT, prove it's really you. Say your catch phrase.
JT，证明真的是你。说你的口头禅。
- [sighs] Kids, let's leave JT alone.
孩子们，我们别打扰JT了。
- Yeah, don't worry. Don't worry.
是的，别担心。别担心。
I got this.
我能搞定。
[clears throat]
清清嗓子
I got this!
我能搞定！
- [laughing] - Both: Whoa! It's JT Steele!
笑着说：哇！是JT·斯蒂尔！
- I cannot wait to tell everybody!
我迫不及待要告诉所有人！
- Yeah. - Ah...Sorry, kids.
是啊。
As much as I know you're dying to brag
抱歉，孩子们。
to all of your friends that a Fan's Choice Award-winning
我知道你们很想向所有朋友炫耀
megastar like myself is staying at your home,
一个像我这样的粉丝选择奖得主巨星住在你们家，
you can't tell anyone I'm here.
但不能告诉任何人我在这里。
all: Aw... - Really?
大家：啊...真的吗？
- Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
If people are hounding JT, then he can't properly prepare
如果人们不断骚扰JT，他就无法好好准备
for the most challenging and heroic role he's ever played...
他迄今为止最具挑战性和英雄色彩的角色...
a suburban dad.
一个郊区的爸爸。
- Are you sure we can't tell anybody?
- 你确定我们不能告诉任何人吗？
- Would you guys like having a movie star
- 你们愿意让一个电影明星
staying at your house?
住在你们家里吗？
all: Yeah!
所有人: 愿意！
- Then you can't tell anyone!
- 那你们就不能告诉任何人！
- All right. Have fun with JT.
- 好吧。和JT好好玩。
- Wait. You're leaving?
- 等等。你要走了？
- Yeah, well, in order for JT to immerse himself into the role,
- 是的，为了让JT完全沉浸在角色中，
your mom and I agreed to clear out.
你妈妈和我决定搬出去。
- It's gonna be really hard to leave you kids,
真的很难离开你们这些孩子，
but we're making this sacrifice for JT.
但为了JT，我们愿意做出这个牺牲。
- If you need us, we'll be at his luxury condo in Vail.
如果你们需要我们，我们会在Vail的豪华公寓里。
- Love you, bye!
爱你们，再见！
- This is awesome!
这太棒了！
- JT Steele is staying at our house.
JT Steele要住在我们家。
- You guys look like you're all ready for bed,
你们看起来都准备好睡觉了，
so... sweet dreams!
那么...做个好梦！
- Um... no, we just woke up.
呃...不，我们刚起床。
- Don't you sass me, young lady.
别跟我顶嘴，小姑娘。
Did that feel real?
那感觉真实吗？
- Ah, could use some work. - Mm-hmm.
啊，还有待改进。
- But really, we have to go to school, JT.
真的，我们得去上学了，JT。
- No, no, no.
不，不，不。
No more JT.
不再有JT了。
From now on... call me "Father."
从现在起...叫我‘父亲’。
Nah, too formal.
不，太正式了。
Um...Papa.
嗯...爸爸。
[doorbell ringing]
门铃响了。
- Who's that? - America.
谁啊？美国。
This is your first mission not do-able.
这是你的第一个任务，看似不可能完成。
Get rid of them!
把他们赶走！
- But if it's not do-able.
但如果这任务真的不可能完成。
How are we gonna do it?
我们该怎么做到呢？
That's what make it exciting!
这就是它的刺激之处！
At first you don't think it's do-able,
一开始你认为不可能完成，
and then you do it!
然后你做到了！
Now, do it! While I do this!
现在，去做吧！我来做这个！
[loud thud]
砰！
- Wow!
哇！
Papa is so cool!
爸爸真是太酷了！
[doorbell ringing]
（门铃响）
- Where is he?
他在哪儿？
- Where is who?
谁在哪儿？
- JT.
JT。
I was on my way to school and I got a BCD blast.
我正要去学校，结果遇到了BCD爆炸。
I want to see JT Steele.
我想见JT Steele。
- Well, he's not here.
嗯，他不在这里。
[metal cracking]
（金属断裂声）
- See? Just Squishy.
看吧？只有Squishy。
- Anyway...
- 总之...
we told the reporter the truth.
我们告诉了记者真相。
He's not here. - Yeah.
他不在这里。 - 是的。
- Do you really think our dad knows JT Steele,
- 你真的认为我们的爸爸认识JT Steele，
and that he actually babysat him as a kid?
并且他实际上在他小时候照顾过他？
- And that JT came here to research a role
- 而且JT来这里是为了研究一个角色
about playing a suburban dad?
关于扮演一个郊区爸爸？
- Uh, they didn't say any of that on the report.
- 呃，他们在报道中没有提到这些。
- Look. I'm your best friend, Mae.
- 听着。我是你最好的朋友，Mae。
Would I lie to you?
我会对你撒谎吗？
- I'd like to think not.
我想我不会。
- Okay, well, see you at school.
好吧，那学校见。
- We completed our first mission!
我们完成了第一个任务！
- Hiya! Hyah!
嗨呀！嘿呀！
I just completed my first mission too.
我也刚刚完成了我的第一个任务。
Lunch!
午餐！
- Oh, what'd you make us? - Don't sass me!
哦，你给我们做了什么？别跟我顶嘴！
- Ooh! That was better.
哦！这样好多了。
- And, you know, it felt better.
而且，你知道，感觉好多了。
Ah, what time does your driver get here?
啊，你的司机几点到这里？
- Oh, we take the bus.
哦，我们坐公交车。
- Ew!
呃！
All right, then I guess I can give you guys some bus money.
好吧，那我想我可以给你们一些公交车费。
Will 100 bucks each cover it?
每人100美元够吗？
- Actually, it's the school bus,
实际上，是校车，
so we don't have to pay.
所以我们不用付钱。
- On the way there...
去的时候...
It's the way back when they get you.
回来的时候他们才收费。
- Mm-hmm. I get it.
嗯，我明白了。
- Wow! Fake Dad made it rain.
哇！假爸爸让钱雨下了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Oh, man. I'm starving.
- 哦，伙计。我快饿死了。
I didn't eat my lunch today.
我今天没吃午饭。
- I couldn't eat my lunch today.
- 我今天也没吃午饭。
JT packed me an onion...
JT给我打包了一个洋葱……
and half a jar of mustard.
还有半瓶芥末酱。
- Well, I got soup.
- 好吧，我带了汤。
- Well, we have to eat before we go home.
- 好吧，我们回家前得吃点东西。
There's no telling what JT is gonna feed us.
谁知道JT会给我们吃什么。
- Already took care of it.
- 已经解决了。
- Okay, I got a large ghost pepper pizza
好的，我拿到了一个大份的鬼椒披萨
and a chicken parm for a Mr. Harper.
还有一份鸡肉帕尔马给哈珀先生。
- I'm Mr. Harper.
我就是哈珀先生。
- Watch out for the spicy ghost pepper.
小心那个辣鬼椒。
It's a wicked scorcher.
它可是个狠角色。
- Keep the change.
不用找零了。
- Thanks, Mr. Harper.
谢谢，哈珀先生。
- Dicky, where'd you get all that money?
迪基，你哪来这么多钱？
- Oh...um...
哦...嗯...
Definitely not from JT Steele, ha.
绝对不是从JT斯蒂尔那里来的，哈。
He's not at our house researching a movie role.
他不在我们家研究电影角色。
- Yeah, you told us.
- 是的，你已经告诉我们了。
- Well, we just want you to be sure he's still not there.
- 嗯，我们只是想确认他是否还在那里。
- We get it.
- 我们明白了。
- A movie star didn't make our lunches.
- 电影明星没有给我们做午餐。
- We believe you.
- 我们相信你。
What would a movie star be doing at your house?
电影明星会在你家做什么？
- Not pretending to be our dad, that's for sure.
- 肯定不是假装成我们的爸爸。
It worked. - Sure did.
这招奏效了。
- Totally.
- 确实奏效了。
- Yeah, nobody knows he's at our house.
是的，没人知道他在我们家。
- This is terrible. - Sure is.
这太糟糕了。
- Totally.
确实。
- I mean, what's the point of having JT Steele at our house
我是说，如果没人知道JT·斯蒂尔在我们家，那我们把JT·斯蒂尔请到家里有什么意义呢？
if nobody knows JT Steele is at our house?
如果没人知道JT·斯蒂尔在我们家，那我们把JT·斯蒂尔请到家里有什么意义呢？
- Then we gotta find a way to tell people JT Steele is at our house
那我们就得想办法让人们知道JT·斯蒂尔在我们家，但又不能直接告诉他们。
without telling people JT Steele is at our house.
跟着我做。
Follow my lead.
所以，你们能相信BCD上的那个关于JT·斯蒂尔在我们家的故事吗？
So, can you guys believe that story on BCD
我是说，真的。JT·斯蒂尔在我们家！
about JT Steele at our house?
JT·斯蒂尔在我们家。
- I mean, seriously. JT Steele at our house!
我是说，真的。JT Steele在我们家！
JT Steele at... our...house.
JT Steele在...我们...家。
- Are you trying to tell us that JT Steele is at your house?
你是想告诉我们JT Steele在你家吗？
- We did not say that.
我们没这么说。
So he's not at your house?
那他不在你家？
- We did not say that.
我们没这么说。
- Okay, I gotta ask.
好吧，我得问一下。
Is he at your house? Is he not at your house?
他在你家吗？他不在你家吗？
- If he... were at our house,
如果他...在我们家，
he may or may not have told us that we could not tell anybody.
他可能告诉我们不能告诉任何人。
Wink.
眨眼。
- Oh, I get it.
- 哦，我明白了。
'Cause if he... were at your house,
因为如果他...在你们家，
then you wouldn't be having us all over
那么你们就不会邀请我们明天去你家
for a barbecue tomorrow to meet him.
参加烧烤派对见他了。
Wink.
眨眼。
- You're right. We would not.
- 你说得对。我们不会。
So we won't be seeing you at 2:00 tomorrow.
所以明天2点我们不会见到你。
Wink.
眨眼。
Oh, wink.
哦，眨眼。
- Okay, now I gotta ask.
好吧，现在我得问了。
Are seeing them at 2:00?
你们是2点见他们吗？
Are we not seeing them at 2:00?
我们不是2点见他们吗？
- Oh, we're seeing them at 2:00.
哦，我们是2点见他们。
At the barbecue JT doesn't know we're having.
在JT不知道的烧烤聚会上。
Yet.
还不知道。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
both: Oh! - Whoa!
哦！ - 哇！
Look at all this luxury!
看看这所有的奢华！
Hot tub! Push-button espresso!
热水浴缸！一键式浓缩咖啡机！
[gasps] Massage chair!
按摩椅！
- Honey, look!
亲爱的，看！
It's JT's Fan's Choice Award
这是JT的‘粉丝选择奖’
for "Mission: Not Do-able 3"!
为了‘任务：不可能3’！
- Ah...
啊...
- Anne, take my picture!
安妮，给我拍张照！
- I'm...busy.
我...正忙着。
- Fine, I'm leaving you out of my acceptance speech.
好吧，我在领奖感言里不提你了。
- Don't care.
无所谓。
- Uh, sometimes... all you need in life is a br--
- 呃，有时候... 生活中你只需要一个...
- [yells] Tom!
- [大喊] 汤姆！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- No, officer. I don't know where they are.
- 不，警官。我不知道他们在哪里。
I haven't seen them in hours.
我已经好几个小时没见到他们了。
Oh!
哦！
Never mind, they just got home.
没关系，他们刚到家。
Where were you?
你去哪儿了？
I have been worried sick about you kids.
我一直在为你俩担心得要命。
- Really?
- 真的？
Oh, we're so sorry.
哦，我们很抱歉。
- Yes!
是的！
You totally believed me! I nailed it!
你完全相信我了！我做到了！
This isn't even a real phone.
这甚至不是一个真正的手机。
It's just my hand. I drew numbers on it.
这只是我的手。我在上面画了数字。
- You know, if you really want to nail being a suburban dad--
你知道，如果你想真正做好一个郊区爸爸——
- If you're gonna say, "sign for a package in my underwear,"
如果你要说，“在我的内裤里签收包裹”，
I already did it.
我已经做过了。
And nailed it!
并且做到了！
Pff! Thank you.
呸！谢谢你。
- Actually, I was thinking more along the lines
实际上，我考虑的是更传统的
of a good-old neighborhood barbecue.
邻里烧烤。
- It's what all dads do. Rocking the apron...
这是所有爸爸都会做的事。系上围裙...
- Grilling up some meat in the yard.
在院子里烤肉。
- It's the only real way to complete your dad-ucation.
这是完成你爸爸教育的唯一真正方式。
all: Barbecue! Barbecue!
烧烤！烧烤！
Barbecue! Barbecue!
- I love it.
我喜欢这个。
It's already got a chant and everything.
它已经有了自己的口号和一切。
As long as it's just us.
只要是我们自己人就行。
- Sure.
当然。
Of course, if you want to do it the way a real dad would, you should--
当然，如果你想像一个真正的父亲那样做，你应该——
You know what? Forget it.
你知道吗？算了。
It's too real.
太真实了。
- No, no. I-I want real.
不，不。我-我想要真实的。
- Okay.
好的。
You'd let us invite three friends over.
你会让我们邀请三个朋友过来。
There, I said it.
我说出来了。
- Well, if that's what a real dad would do,
好吧，如果这是一个真正的父亲会做的事，
then consider it done!
那就这么定了！
- Oh, yeah! - [bell ringing] - Speaking of done.
哦，是的！ - [铃声响起] - 说到完成。
- Yeah, a little too done.
是的，有点太完成了。
- Maybe having a barbecue is not a good idea.
也许举办烧烤派对不是个好主意。
- No, no, no. It's okay.
不，不，不。没关系。
- Yeah, everybody burns dinner now and then.
是啊，每个人偶尔都会把饭烧糊。
- Uhm... this wasn't your dinner.
嗯...这不是你的晚餐。
- What? - It was your laundry.
什么？ - 是你的洗衣物。
Uh...
呃...
It's the typical dad mess-up. Am I right?
这是典型的爸爸失误。我说得对吗？
Tell me I'm right.
告诉我我说得对。
all: Uh... - No, seriously.
嗯... - 不，说真的。
I'm here to learn. Give me the truth.
我是来学习的。告诉我真相。
- Fine. You sent us to school with $400 and soup in a bag.
- 好吧。你给了我们400美元和一袋汤去上学。
- You thought we were missing and you called the police on your hand.
- 你以为我们失踪了，然后用自己的手报警。
- And we haven't seen the dog since he was on your head.
- 还有，自从狗在你头上之后，我们就没见过它了。
- I'm not following you,
- 我不明白你在说什么，
so just give me the headline of this review.
所以直接告诉我这个评价的要点。
- Okay.
- 好的。
"JT Steele...
“JT·斯蒂尔...”
you don't got this."
“你还没掌握。”
- How can you say that?
- 你怎么能这么说？
- You said you wanted the truth.
- 你说过你想听真话。
- No actor wants the truth. I was acting!
- 没有演员想要听真话。我只是在演戏！
- It's all right. You'll be fine for the barbecue.
- 没关系。你会在烧烤会上表现很好的。
- Yeah. - Barbecue?
- 是啊。 - 烧烤？
I can't pull off a barbecue.
我应付不了烧烤。
Only dads or actors who can play dads can barbecue.
只有爸爸或者能扮演爸爸的演员才能烧烤。
And since I'm no good at either,
而且因为我两者都不擅长，
I quit.
我退出。
- Being a dad or acting?
- 当爸爸还是演戏？
- Both.
- 两者都是。
I'm quitting... "dacting."
我放弃... "扮演爸爸"。
Now... if you'll excuse me.
现在... 如果你们不介意。
[sobbing]
[哭泣]
- But the barbecue is still on, right?
- 但是烧烤还在进行，对吧？
- [sobbing]
- [哭泣]
- Maybe we should call for help. - Yeah.
- 也许我们应该求助。 - 是的。
- It's ringing. - Stop.
- 正在响铃。 - 停下。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
♪
- This is not good.
- 这不太好。
- No, Mom. Everything's great here.
- 不，妈妈。这里一切都很好。
We didn't break anything.
我们什么都没弄坏。
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
- Yeah, nothing broken here either.
- 是的，这里也没坏什么。
- [sobbing]
- [哭泣]
- Love you, Mom. Talk to you tomorrow.
- 爱你，妈妈。明天再聊。
Okay, I think she bought it.
好的，我想她信了。
- What are we gonna do?
- 我们该怎么办？
- Mae, Molly, and Natlee are coming over tomorrow
- Mae、Molly和Natlee明天要来烧烤。
for a barbecue.
来个烧烤派对。
- Maybe he just needs to sleep it off.
也许他只是需要睡一觉就好。
I'm sure he'll be fine in the morning.
我确信他早上就会没事的。
- Well, that didn't work.
好吧，那招没奏效。
- [crying]
（哭泣声）
- Did you sleep with your shoes on?
你是不是穿着鞋子睡的？
- No. [coughs]
没有。（咳嗽声）
I couldn't sleep at all.
我根本睡不着。
I was up all night contemplating everything I'm bad at:
我整晚都在思考我不擅长的事情：
Laundry-ing, dacting
洗衣服，打字
- Not actual words.
- 不是实际的词。
- [groans] Word thinking.
- [呻吟] 思考词。
- Look, you're over thinking this.
- 瞧，你过度思考了。
You can totally host a barbecue.
你完全可以举办一个烧烤派对。
Just do what your dad did when you were a kid.
就像你小时候你爸爸做的那样。
I bet you're a chip off the old block.
我打赌你继承了你爸爸的优点。
- Wait, wait.
- 等等，等等。
Did you just say "chip"?
你刚才说的是“碎片”吗？
"Block"?
“块”？
And "off"?
还有“离开”？
- I sure did.
我确实说了。
- I haven't used those words since my dad went down the block
自从我爸去街角买薯条然后离开后，
for chips and took off.
我就再也没用过那些词了。
He never came back.
他再也没有回来。
I just waited there with a bowl full of dip.
我只能拿着一碗蘸酱在那里等。
With nothing to scoop it with...
没有东西可以舀蘸酱……
but my finger.
只能用我的手指。
That's it!
就是这样！
I had no chips! - Okay.
我没有薯条！
- No chips.
没有薯条。
No chips.
没有薯片。
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Man, he really wanted chips.
这家伙真的很想吃薯片。
- Yeah, he went out hard.
是啊，他拼命想吃。
What was in there?
里面是什么？
- It's warm milk.
温牛奶。
- What are we gonna do now?
我们现在怎么办？
- We can't host a barbecue for our friends,
如果我们朋友的烧烤派对，他睡得死死的，我们可办不了。
if he's sound asleep.
或者说，他可以吗？嗯...
- Or can he?
或者他能吗？
Hmm...
嗯...
all: Hmm...
大家：嗯...
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[doorbell ringing]
[门铃响]
- Where's JT? - Or where is not JT?
JT在哪儿？
Wink.
眨眼。
- Actually...
实际上...
JT is not here.
JT不在这里。
all: Aw...
大家：啊...
- Wink.
眨眼。
- Ladies, meet Fan's Choice Award-winner...
女士们，认识一下Fan's Choice Award得主...
JT Steele!
JT Steele！
- Hey, ladies. What's up?
嘿，女士们。怎么样？
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Hold on!
等等！
Give the man some space.
给这位先生一些空间。
- JT's a space man.
JT是个太空人。
- It looks like JT, but his lips weren't moving.
看起来像JT，但他的嘴唇没动。
- And I'm pretty sure he's snoring.
而且我很确定他在打呼噜。
- Nope, he's just practicing his breathing exercises
不，他只是在练习他的呼吸练习
for an upcoming movie where he plays a Navy SEAL.
为了即将上映的电影，他在里面扮演一个海豹突击队员。
- Arr, arr, arr, arr, arr, arr, arr.
啊，啊，啊，啊，啊，啊，啊。
- Who is also an actual seal.
而且他还是一只真正的海豹。
- That doesn't sound like a real movie.
这听起来不像是一部真正的电影。
- Something's a little weird.
有点奇怪。
- Nope. Nothing weird.
不，没什么奇怪的。
Okay, well, we'll see you at school
好吧，我们学校见
where you can tell everyone that you met JT Steele at our house.
你可以告诉所有人你在我们家遇到了JT·斯蒂尔。
- But... we came for a barbecue.
但是...我们是来吃烧烤的。
- I skipped breakfast for this.
- 我为了这个连早餐都没吃。
- That's right. Barbecue.
- 没错，烧烤。
JT's gonna grill us up some burgers.
JT要给我们烤些汉堡。
This should be fun to watch.
这应该会很有趣。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Let's take the long way.
我们绕远路吧。
That way we'll give JT plenty of time to prepare.
这样我们可以给JT足够的时间准备。
Don't look back.
别回头看。
- How are we gonna pull off this barbecue?
- 我们怎么搞这个烧烤？
- I'm gonna need my big spatula and a lot of duct tape.
- 我需要我的大铲子和很多胶带。
[upbeat music]
- That was the longest long way ever.
- 那真是史上最长的绕路。
- I don't understand why we had to go around the block.
- 我不明白我们为什么要绕过街区。
- Oh, hey, JT's already manning the grill.
- 哦，嘿，JT已经在烤架前忙碌了。
- Hey, girls. Welcome to the barbecue.
- 嘿，女孩们。欢迎来到烧烤派对。
- Uh, no, no, no, no, no.
- 呃，不，不，不，不，不。
Not so close. Give him some space.
不要靠得太近。给他点空间。
- Just watching the master at work.
- 只是看着大师工作。
- Don't worry, guys. I grill this.
- 别担心，伙计们。我来烤这个。
- Thanks, JT.
- 谢谢，JT。
- The meat is raw.
- 肉还是生的。
- Is that grill even hot?
- 那烤架热了吗？
- What are we supposed to eat?
- 我们到底要吃什么？
- There's not even any chips.
- 连薯片都没有。
Just dip.
只有蘸酱。
- Well, at least you got to meet JT Steele.
- 好吧，至少你见到了JT Steele。
And he got to... "meat" you.
而他也有机会...“认识”你。
All right, see you guys at school,
好了，学校见，
where you can tell everyone that we know him.
到时候你可以告诉所有人我们认识他。
- There's JT.
- 那是JT。
- It's Sharon Dee. - From BCD!
- 是Sharon Dee。 - 来自BCD！
all: TV?
所有人: 电视？
- Oh! Oh!
- 哦！哦！
- Let's get him out of here.
- 我们把他弄出去。
- Quick! Come one, guys!
- 快！快点，伙计们！
- Come on, come on. Oh! [loud thud]
- 快点，快点。哦！[大声的撞击声]
all: Oh...
所有人: 哦...
- [grunting]
- [咕哝声]
- This is bad. - Really bad.
- 这很糟糕。 - 真的很糟糕。
- Could be worse.
- 可能会更糟。
- Yeah, at least that reporter
是啊，至少那个记者还不知道他退出演艺圈了。
doesn't know he quit show business.
全员：迪奇！- 对不起。
all: Dicky! - Sorry.
[耳语] 那不是对你说的。
[whispering] That wasn't meant for you.
- 他要退出演艺圈？
- He's quitting show business?
你真的退出演艺圈了吗？
Is it true that you quit show business?
[咕哝声]
- [grunts]
- 我听上去像是肯定的。
- Sounds like a yes to me.
你们在这里第一个听到这个消息。
You heard it here first.
哦，不。这都是我们的错。
- Oh, no. This is all our fault.
JT·斯蒂尔的职业生涯就要因为我们毁了。
JT Steele's career is about to be ruined because of us.
JT Steele的事业即将因为我们而毁于一旦。
- What are we supposed to do?
我们应该怎么办？
- We gotta make him a hero again.
我们必须让他再次成为英雄。
- How?
怎么做？
- With chips.
用薯片。
- Uhm, excuse me. He's not quitting the business.
呃，不好意思。他并没有退出娱乐圈。
He's just researching the role of a down-on-his-luck dad
他只是在研究一个倒霉父亲的角
who rescues a pathetic barbecue.
色，这个父亲拯救了一个可怜的烧烤。
Perhaps you'd like to see a scene.
也许你们想看看一个场景。
- Roll camera.
开拍。
- Look how pathetic this barbecue is.
- 看看这个烧烤有多可怜。
All of the children are so sad.
所有的孩子们都这么难过。
- Why are they sad?
- 他们为什么难过？
They've got a big bowl of dip.
他们有一大碗蘸酱。
- Shouldn't they be happy?
- 他们不应该高兴吗？
- They would be happy, but they have...
- 他们本该高兴，但他们没有……
no chips.
没有薯片。
all: No chips.
所有人：没有薯片。
No chips.
没有薯片。
- No chips.
No way!
不可能！
I got this!
我搞定这个！
Real quick, where am I?
快点，我在哪儿？
- Boulder.
博尔德。
- That's right.
没错。
Chip-a-doodle-doo!
薯片来啦！
Hyah!
嘿！
- Wow! That really snapped him out of it.
哇！这真的让他清醒了。
- Okay, it'll take him about a half-hour
好的，他大概需要半小时
to find chips and bring them back.
找到薯片并带回来。
So all--
所以所有--
- Chipee-ki-yay! Daddy's back!
- 薯片奇侠归来！爸爸回来了！
- How did you get back here so quick?
- 你怎么这么快就回来了？
- Because I'm a dad.
- 因为我是爸爸。
And that's what dads do.
这就是爸爸做的事。
Also, there was a minivan next door with a bunch of free chips in the back.
而且隔壁有一辆小型货车，后面有一堆免费的薯片。
- I think he stole Ms. Hoolihan's groceries.
- 我觉得他偷了霍利汉女士的杂货。
- Who wants chips with their dip?
- 谁想要薯片配蘸酱？
- Ooh, I do. all: I do, I do.
- 哦，我想要。大家: 我想要，我想要。
- Another stellar performance from JT Steele.
- JT·斯蒂尔的又一次精彩表演。
- Ah, I couldn't have pulled it off
- 啊，没有我的四位小舞蹈教练，我可做不到。
without my four little dacting coaches.
- 还是一句话都没说。 - [笑]
- Still not a word. - [laughs]
好吧，我在这里的工作完成了。
Well, my job here is done.
我现在要回好莱坞了。
I'm gonna go back to Hollywood now.
[吹口哨]
[whistling]
我不知道为什么，但我有个想法
I don't know why, but I had this idea
关于我参演一部海豹电影的。
about me being in a seal movie.
[直升机旋翼呼呼作响]
[helicopter blades whirring]
再见了，孩子们！ - 再见！
See ya, kids! - Bye!
再见，孩子们！ - 拜拜！
- Yeah, this is my helicopter! - Woah! Cool helicopter.
- 是的，这是我的直升机！ - 哇！酷炫的直升机。
- I own it!
- 我拥有它！
- Is that JT?
- 那是JT吗？
- Yep!
- 是的！
He's a terrible dad!
他是个糟糕的爸爸！
But he sure knows how to leave a barbecue!
但他确实知道如何离开烧烤派对！
[upbeat music]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪